Guide to the Hospitality Leadership: The Cornell Hotel School research papers, 1920-1999.
Hospitality Leadership The Cornell Hotel School research papers
- Letter regarding the creation of a hotel school. / Letter regarding a convention in Iowa. / Letter of possible acceptance of an invitation to a convention in Iowa., 11/28/1922; 02/04/1926; 02/02/1926; Letters, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 4, Folder 257)
  Author: Howie, John / Meek, Howard / E. Statler
  Recipient: Dudley, Frank / Betten, Cornelius / Meek, Howard
- "Questions for Lois Jean Meek", None; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 258)
  Additional description: List of questions to ask Meek. Attached transcript of the interview.
  Recipient: Brown, Dick
- Several letters regarding the Hotel School, Various; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 6 (Box 3, Folder 259)
- "Cornell--Ten Years After", Feb-35; News Article, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 260)
  Additional description: Copy of article printed in Hotel Management about 10 year anniversary of Hotel School.
  Author: W.R. Needham
- Recollections of an alumni's experiences at the Hotel School., 10/18/1995; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 261)
  Author: Fors, Dick
- "Reflections of Cornell Hotel School" / "Hotel School Memories" / "Faculty Reminiscences", Unknown; 10/16/1995; 10/05/1995; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 3, Folder 262)
  Additional description: 1st is an alumni's reflections of the Hotel School. Last two are mini-biographies of Various faculty and staff members.
  Author: Stover, Frank / Bantuvanis, George (2)
  Recipient: Chiu, Michael / Unknown
- "One perspective on the School's 50th Anniversary", 10/23/1995; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 263)
  Additional description: Description of the Hotel School's 50th Anniversary celebration.
  Author: Sansbury, Michael
- "Who Meant The Most" / None / None, 10/19/1995; 10/24/1995; 10/19/1995; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 3 (Box 3, Folder 264)
  Additional description: Explanation of what professor meant the most. / Hotel School anecdotes (last 2)
  Author: Duchscherer, James / Nirula, Lalit / Kappa, Margaret
- Letters regarding requests sent out for highlights of the Hotel School from alumni., Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 3, Folder 265)
  Author: numerous
- Letters regarding requests sent out for highlights of the Hotel School from alumni., Various; Letters, Copy No. of pieces: 6 (Box 3, Folder 266)
- 2 boards with charts of undergraduate enrollment and staffing statistics from 1969-1979 glued to them., None; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 2 (Box 3, Folder 267)
- "Memorandum of Understanding between the American Hotel Association and the Cornell University Governing Financial Support and Conduct of a Course of Training for Hotel Officers to be Given by the State College of Agriculture", 1/12/1924; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 268)
  Author: American Hotel Association
  Recipient: Dudley, Frank
- Letters w/ highlights of alumni experiences at the Hotel School., 10/12/1995; 10/16/1995; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 3, Folder 269)
  Author: Hunsberger, Christopher / Petzing, James
- Various pamphlets from the University of Nevada Las Vegas College of Hotel Administration. One pamphlet from University of Massachusetts Amherst., None; Pamphlets, Original No. of pieces: 6 (Box 3, Folder 270)
  Author: Various Writers
- "Hospitality Leader" / MSU HRIM / "Hospitality Programs" / "Master of Science Degrees in Hospitality Industry Studies Tourism and Travel Management", None; Pamphlets, Original No. of pieces: 4 (Box 3, Folder 271)
  Additional description: A newsletter and pamphlet from Michigan State University's hospitality program. / 2 brochures from NYU's hospitality program.
- Copies of several pages of Various book and articles regarding hotel management, including Cornell's rank (#1)., None; Pamphlet, Copy No. of pieces: 5 (Box 3, Folder 272)
- "Bulletin of the Cornell Society Of Hotelmen", Various; New Articles, Copy No. of pieces: 7 (Box 3, Folder 273)
  Additional description: Several issues of the bulletin.
- "Cornell University and the Course in Hotel Administration", Apr-34; New Article, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 274)
  Additional description: Article about the Hotel School in Hotel Bulletin and The Nation's Chefs.
  Author: Vehling, Joseph
- "Chronology of Hotel/Motelkeeping, 1900-1985", Unknown; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 275)
  Additional description: Timeline of hotel/motel keeping.
- "Young Hotelmen Create Air Bases Across Central Africa" / others, 09/07/1994; 12/1942; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 276)
  Additional description: Letter, attached copy of article in The Hotel Monthly
  Author: Howard, Kevin (2)
  Recipient: Sullivan, Michael / None
- Chapter VII: The School of Hotel Administration and Institutes Management, 3/21/1995; Book, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 277)
  Additional description: Story of the founding of the Hotel School
  Author: George
  Recipient: Bernice
- Several correspondences regarding the HH Book., Various; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 4 (Box 3, Folder 278)
- "Telegrams relating to the appointment of Howard B. Meek" / others, Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 5 (Box 3, Folder 279)
  Additional description: 09/23/1922; 02/24/1922; Various; 09/11/1922; 12/19/1994. Letter notifying Meek of his appointment as Assistant Professor of Institutional Management in the School of Home Economics of the College of Agriculture. / Report on the progress of the Educational Committee on the proposed Hotel School. / Various telegrams related to the appointment of Meek. / Letter of acceptance to position. Letter w/ comments on chapter 1 of HH Book and photos.
  Author: Dean Mann / Dudley, Frank / Various / Meek, Howard / Chiu, Michael
  Recipient: Meek, Howard / American Hotel Association / Various / Dean Mann / Marcham, John
- Letter regarding what the purpose of each of the future Agriculture buildings will be. / Letter regarding establishing a hotel school. / Letter regarding permission to create courses for hotel training. / Letter regarding the creation of hotel training courses., Various; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 4 (Box 3, Folder 280)
  Additional description: 12/19/1919; 01/20/1921; 06/24/1921; 02/12/1921.
  Author: illegible / Dudley, Frank / Dean Mann / Van Rensselaer, Martha
  Recipient: Green, Elmore / Schurman, Jacob / Rose, Flora / Dean Mann
- "American Hotels in 1848" / "The Palaces of the People", 1973; 1968; Book, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 3, Folder 281)
  Additional description: copies of two chapters in two different books
  Author: King, Doris / White, Arthur
- "From The Beginning" / "Food for Thought", Jan-94; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 3, Folder 282)
  Additional description: Article about the history of Nation's Restaurant News / Foodservice statistics.
  Author: Hayes, Jack / Unknown
- Random articles and correspondences regarding the Hotel School, including one about the history of unions in the School., Various; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 3, Folder 283)
- "John McFarlane Howie: The Forgotten Godfather of the Cornell School of Hotel Administration", 10/1/1993; Book, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 284)
  Additional description: Summer research project on Howie from an associate professor at Niagara University. Attached letter to Glenn Withiam regarding a manuscript he was asked to read.
  Author: Howell, David
- The Register of Ye Hosts, 5/7/1926; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 285)
  Additional description: photocopied newsletter, highlights on articles about Ezra Cornell opening. Attached handwritten notes.
- Letter regarding a convention. / 3 letters to Meek's nephew Don about Various topics. / Letter about Various topics., Various; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 5 (Box 3, Folder 286)
  Additional description: 07/07/1924; 06/08/1926; 03/27/1934; 08/19/1934; 10/29/1947.
  Author: Howie, John / Meek, Howard (3) / Howie, John
  Recipient: Howard Meek / Don (3) / Hamilton, W.
- Transcript of the first interview with Professor Meek., 5/14/1964; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 287)
  Author: Carol, Sharon
- The Hotel News, Various; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 288)
  Additional description: Copies of several articles through the early 1940's in The Hotel News.
- Pan-American Airways-Africa, LTD., Dec-42; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 289)
  Additional description: Article in New Horizons.
  Author: Howard, Kevin
- Several anecdotes from Vinnicombe. / Several endorsements of the Hotel School from other hotelmen. / Letter regarding Meek wanting to build a Hotel School., Unknown; Unknown; 05/20/1943; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 3, Folder 290)
  Author: Vinnicombe, Ed / Unknown / Howie, John
  Recipient: None / None / Heasley, Walter
- Memo and copy of the inventory of materials currently available for history project, suggested outline., 12/15/1989; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 291)
  Author: Conner, Fred
  Recipient: Peckenpaugh, Norm
- Mary Wright Class of '45, None; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 292)
  Additional description: Transcript of tape recorded interview with Mary Wright
- Folder containing several budget calculations for the construction of Statler Hall, along with a reprint of the August 1950 copy of Hotel Monthly magazine w/ the story of Statler Hall., Various; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: Many (Box 3, Folder 293)
- The Cornell Innkeeper / The Innkeeper / None / The Hotel Gazette, Various; 10/31/1958; None; 05/11/1957; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 4 (Box 3, Folder 294)
  Additional description: several articles in the paper over Various years. / Half of an issue of The Innkeeper / Chapter 4 of the HH Book outline / several pages from the Hotel Gazette.
- Response to a letter requesting a hotel be built on campus for the hotel courses., 12/18/1923; 11/26/1923; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 295)
  Author: Mann, A.R.
  Recipient: Rose, Flora / Rose, Flora, Van Rensselaer, Martha, Meek, Howard
- Various budget plans for the Statler project, Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 3, Folder 296)
- Various articles regarding Statler (the man and the building) and planning and development on Cornell's Campus, Various; Magazine, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 3, Folder 297)
- Various documents related to the Statler building project., Various; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: Various (Box 3, Folder 298)
- Numerous budget plans for the Statler Hall renovation that took place in the late '80's., Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: Many (Box 3, Folder 299)
- The Cornell Hotel and Restaurant Administration Quarterly, May-85; Book, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 300)
  Additional description: Silver anniversary issue
- "From a Closet Under the Stairs", 1988; Book, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 301)
  Additional description: Book about the history of the Hotel School from 1921 to 1950
  Author: Sayles, Charles
- Hotel related news articles., Various; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 302)
- "Literature of the Lodging Market:, 1966; Book, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 3, Folder 303)
  Additional description: Copied article and handwritten notes
  Author: Borsenik, Frank
- Outline for Chapter Five, 3/25/1995; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 3, Folder 305)
  Additional description: Outline for Chapter 5
- Transcript of interview w/ Dean Robert Beck, None Given; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 306)
- Transcription of Dean Clark interview, None given; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 307)
- 1981-1982 Annual Report, 7/30/1982; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 308)
  Author: Clark, John
  Recipient: Kennedy, Keith
- Annual reports: 1st is 1982-1983, 2nd is 1983-1984, 07/22/1983; 09/07/1984; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 3, Folder 309)
  Author: Clark, Jack (both)
  Recipient: Kennedy, Keith / Provost Barker
- 1984-1985 Annual Report on the Hotel School, 8/26/1985; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 310)
  Author: Clark Dean
  Recipient: Provost Baker
- Annual report on the Hotel School, 1985-1986; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 311)
- Interview w/ Jack Clark, None Given; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 3, Folder 312)
- The Bulletin, Various; Magazine, Original No. of pieces: 7 (Box 3, Folder 313)
  Additional description: 7 issues of The Cornell Society of Hotelmen's magazine, The Bulletin
- The Hotel Monthly / Southern Hotel Journal / The Cornell Innkeeper, 08/1950; 12/1948; Spring 1959; Magazine, Original No. of pieces: 3 (Box 4, Folder 314)
  Additional description: 3 magazines featuring stories about Statler
- "The Cornell School of Hotel Administration Master of Hospitality Management Program", None; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 315)
  Additional description: Information on the Masters program
- Hand written letter w/ anecdotes and information about Shellenberger's time at Cornell., 6/1/1994; Letter, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 316)
  Author: Shellenberger, Martin
  Recipient: Sullivan, Michael
- Interview w/ Robert Beck about an incident that took place in 1969, None; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 317)
- "Slaterville Hilton and the First Lady", None; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 318)
  Additional description: Chapter 5 sidebar on Jan Beck and the Beck family
  Recipient:
- Various articles and correspondence regarding the book, including Littum's take on the WSH Takeover and the radical events of the time., None; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 5 (Box 4, Folder 319)
- "Role, Scope and Authority of Triad", None; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 320)
  Additional description: Explanation of the purpose and duties of the Triad Committee
- More of the history of the Beck family, None; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 321)
  Author: Robin, Susan, and Janyce Beck
  Recipient: Edmonson, Brad
- Handwritten notes about a meeting w/ Beck in New Haven, CT., 7/18/1994; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 322)
- "The Hotel School", None; Pamphlet, Original No. of pieces: 2 (Box 4, Folder 323)
  Additional description: List of requirements for graduation, and Hotel School pamphlet for 1989-1990.
- Hotel history photo captions, None; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 324)
  Additional description: information on the photo captions to be put in the HH Book
- Information and several articles about the new master's program, 10/11/1995; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 325)
  Author: Geller, Neal
- "Directions for the Future: Mission, Values, Strategy, and Implementation", None; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 326)
  Additional description: The Strategic Planning Committee's action plans for academic year 1991-1992.
  Author: Clark, Jack
  Recipient: Edmondson, Brad
- "Prof. Beck plants Hotel's flag in France and it's saluted" / others, 12/20/1995; 11/1982; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 4, Folder 327)
  Additional description: Copied information about Dean Dittman / Article about a new 2 year Cornell Hotel School in France.
  Author: Butler, Dave / Burke, Barbara
  Recipient: Dittman, David / None
- The Bulletin / The Hotel School News, Fall 1990 / Summer 1994; Magazine, Original No. of pieces: 2 (Box 4, Folder 328)
  Additional description: 2 Hotelie magazines
- Cornell News articles about the Hotel School set aside as possible sidebars., Various; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 12 (Box 4, Folder 329)
- Interview with Dean Dittman w/ handwritten notes, 9/10/1998; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 330)
- "Study Thyself", Jun-94; New Article, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 331)
  Additional description: Article in Lodging magazine about David Dittman
  Author: Cassedy, Kathleen
- "Cornell's Five-Star School" / "The Adventures of Tom Neuhaus and His Fabulous Computerized Cookbook", None; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 4, Folder 332)
  Additional description: Copied articles from Unknown source
  Author: Zelickson, Jill / Kaff, Albert
- Handwritten notes on Dittman, 07/02/19??; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 333)
- "Milestones in History" / None, 1955/1963; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 4, Folder 334)
  Additional description: List of milestones in Cornell's History / Biography of Martha Van Rensselaer
  Author: Warters, Vivien / Fox, Edith
- Handwritten notes, None; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 335)
- Information Sheets and Letters about Various people, Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 8 (Box 4, Folder 336)
- "The Cornell Hotel Course from 1922 to 1932" / "Cornell's New 1931 Summer Hotel Course", 02/1932; 06/1931; New Article, Original No. of pieces: 2 (Box 4, Folder 337)
  Additional description: Articles about the Hotel School in Hotel Management and The Hotel Monthly magazines.
  Author: Meek, Howard (2)
- "European Chapter Cornell Society of Hotelmen 30th Anniversary Book 1961-1991", None; Book, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 338)
  Additional description: Book about the history of the European chapter of CSH.
  Author: Ed. Evensen, Leif and Streuli, Peter
- A copy of Michael Egan's bio and a lot of articles about him and his role as Chairman of Alamo Rent-A-Car., 5/15/1995; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: Many (Box 4, Folder 339)
  Author: Richardson, Sandy
  Recipient: Apfel, Ira
- "Menu 26th Hotel Ezra Cornell" / "What H.E.C. Means to the Student Body", 1951/1952; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 4, Folder 340)
  Additional description: Menu for the 26th HEC and copy of part of The Cornell Innkeeper w/ articles about the 27th HEC.
- Letter of invitation to HEC 70: Mosaic of Time, w/ part of 2 articles and a photo attached., 2/10/1995; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 341)
  Recipient: Perfetto, Carlo
- "Menus: Their use and collection in an academic library", 07 and 08 of 1991; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 342)
  Additional description: Copy of an article in C&RL News about Cornell's menu collection
  Author: Laurence, Katherine
- "The Team Project in Cornell's Redesigned Professional Master's Program", None; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 343)
  Additional description: Article in Hospitality in Review.
  Author: Lefever, Michael
- Letter of notice about the opening of the School of Hotel Administration in Canberra, Australia., 5/5/1995; Letter, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 344)
  Author: Vallen, Jerome
  Recipient: Educator
- "The Story of Needham & Grohmann, INC." / others, 05/11/1995; 1971; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 3 (Box 4, Folder 345)
  Additional description: Note, article, and handwritten notes about Needham and Grohmann, INC.
  Author: Heinsius, Howard / Grohmann, Vic
- "Odyssey of Eating Out", Jan-94; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 346)
  Additional description: Photocopied article in Nation's Restaurant News.
  Author: Carlino, Bill
- Interview with Beck, David Burak's reply to the story., None; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 347)
- "Financing Expansion: The Hilton-Statler Merger", None given; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 348)
  Additional description: Article about the Hilton-Statler merger.
  Author: Binns, Joseph
- Note regarding the intro, attached "Chronology of Hospitality Industry 1900-1976", 5/8/1995; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 349)
  Recipient: Sullivan, Mike
- "Born to the Business: Joe Baum", May-83; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 350)
  Additional description: Article printed in the Cornell H.R.A. Quarterly.
  Author: Bernstein, Charles
- Letters regarding additions and changes to book, 06/30/1995; Unknown; 07/05/1995; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 4, Folder 351)
  Author: Brad / Marcham, John / (2)
  Recipient: Marcham, John / Unknown / Ira and Brad
- "Robert M. Rosenberg: The People Connection", None; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 352)
  Additional description: Article in the Cornell H.R.A. Quarterly about the chairman of Dunkin' Donuts
- Information on and interview with John Clark, Oct-94; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 353)
  Author: Not Listed
- Profiles of Judi Brownell and Florence Berger, None; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 4, Folder 354)
- Handwritten notes about people, None; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 355)
- Note about sidebars, and attached Burger King sidebar. / More notes about the HH Book., 05/02/1995; 05/06/1995; 05/10/1995; Memo, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 4, Folder 356)
  Author: Brad / Marcham, John (the rest)
  Recipient: Marcham, John, Phil W., and Ira / Brad, Ira, and Glenn / Brad and Ira
- Handwritten notes on different people, None; Multi-format, Original No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 357)
- "Spot light on the Students", Spring,1961; New Article, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 4, Folder 358)
  Additional description: Several articles about international students at the Hotel School
  Author: Not listed
- A list of the major requests for the purchase and/or donation of Statler Inn's inventory., 7/17/1986; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 359)
  Author: HMK
  Recipient: JJC, AAL, AND DCD
- 8 copies of the same letter to Doney about the Wee Stinky Glen lighting, 5/2/1990; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 4, Folder 360)
  Author: Keithan, Bill
  Recipient: Doney, Henry
- Letters regarding costs to renovate the Four Seasons room., 03/11/1990; 03/06/1990; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 2 (Box 4, Folder 361)
  Author: Keithan, Bill / Wallis, Chris
  Recipient: Wallis, Chris / Keithan, Bill
- All documents are regarding the suggested changes to the Wee Stinky Glen lighting, except for one about the 4 Seasons room being remodeled., 03/19/1990; 02/23/1990; 03/15/1990; 02/09/1990; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 4 (Box 4, Folder 362)
  Author: Keithan, Bill / Bacon, Ralph / Doney, Henry / Keithan, Bill
  Recipient: Doney, Henry and Cox, Phillip / Keithan, Bill / Keithan, Bill / Wallis, Chris
- Estimated budget for Statler Inn renovation, 11/18/1983; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 1 (Box 4, Folder 363)
  Author: Penner, Richard and Rosemann, Charles
- "Arts Center Construction is Postponed" / others, Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 4 (Box 4, Folder 364)
  Additional description: 08/23/1984; 08/30/1984; 03/04/1984; 08/24/1984. 2 short memos regarding the completion status of construction in the Inn. / Note about alternate use of lower level Rathskeller Bar and sketch of area. / Cornell Daily Sun article on Schwartz Center construction
  Author: Unknown (2) / Peckenpaugh, Norm / Martens, Heather
  Recipient: Unknown (2) / Statler Club Board of Directors / None
- Letters are all regarding a guest's complaint that the windows in the rooms opened too far and a child could fall through., 06/22/1990; 06/04/1990; 05/02/1990; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 3 (Box 4, Folder 365)
  Author: Keith, Bill / GLM / Palmer, Larry
  Recipient: Palmer, Larry / NLP / Keithan, William
- "Trouble Checks in at Statler" / "Dean Announces New Academic Affairs Team" / others, Various; Multi-format, Copy No. of pieces: 7 (Box 4, Folder 366)